Cameron Dugan

A hard working curiosity driven sophomore Computer Science student with a strong focus on effectiveness through efficiency and readability.

PROJECTS

Deeper Edge Analytics - Volunteer Developer

Responsible for optimizing code, modularizing data analysis, and managing network infrastructure. It is a research project with the Boston Ice Dance Collective and the Micheli Center for Sports to identify common movement patterns using wearable sensor technology with a strong focus on analyzing data for Machine Learning.

Python Image Generator

Creating a program in Python to generate an image from an incomplete copy of the original. Used the most basic statistical model trained on one image at once. Project can be downloaded at https://gitlab.com/cameron.dugan/python-image-dreamer, and some examples can be seen at https://camerondugan.com/Dream-Bot/

AutoDrop

A local network multithreaded peer to peer file sharing with sha256 checksum file validation. Open sourced at https://github.com/dugancatwit/AutoDrop. Developed for a network programming course.

EDUCATION

Wentworth Institute of Technology, Boston, MA

Bachelors of Science in Computer Science, anticipated May 2024.

The Academy for Science and Design, Nashua, NH, May 2020

Top New Hampshire highschool focused on STEM fields.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Eagle Scout - Boy Scouts of America, Troop 272

Held various leadership roles including the highest leadership role in the Troop, and developed skills to work successfully as a team. Performed countless hours of volunteering and community service.

MIT Battle Code Finalist

Competed in a restrictive Java programming competition with college level students. As a team of highschool seniors our placed in the top 13 teams overall in the final tournament.

New Hampshire Scholar

An award for students who completed extra courses, maintained a minimum of a 3.2 cumulative GPA and completed a highschool internship. The internship completed was to help a local author maintain and update her website.

(603) 703-4018

cam@camerondugan.com
http://camerondugan.com/projects/

Development Experience

VR Software in Godot
Microcontroller Software in C++
Mobile and Desktop in Flutter/Dart
Websites in Flutter, Jekyll, and HTML

Programming Languages

Java, C++, Python, Dart, Lua, Rust, Git, and Bash.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Patricks Pub, Gilford NH Dishwasher

June 2021 - August 2021 Worked as a dishwasher and helped with food prep.

Dominos, Nashua NH Customer Service Rep

June 2020 - August 2020 Processed customers orders over the phone and in person, prepared all food items on the menu, and helped delivery drivers with dishes and folding boxes.

City Room Cafe, Nashua NH Dishwasher Part Time

July 2019 - March 2020 Worked in the kitchen of a small diner before covid hit.

Hidden Valley Scout Camp Dishwasher

Summer of 2018 and 2019 Worked in a team that balanced the needs of the chefs and the growing pile of dirty dishes.